offerstation.com 2016-11-22

# Contact Us | OfferStation.com

PRIVACY POLICY

OfferStation takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

 **What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how OfferStation treats personal information that OfferStation collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available without your consent.   
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that OfferStation does not own or control or to people that OfferStation does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**   

  * OfferStation collects personal information when you register with OfferStation, when you use OfferStation products and services, when you visit OfferStation's pages or the pages of certain OfferStation partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. OfferStation may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some products and services we may also ask for your address and contact number. Once you register with OfferStation and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * OfferStation collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. 
  * OfferStation may use the information for the following general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

OfferStation does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with OfferStation under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help OfferStation communicate with you about offers from OfferStation and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of OfferStation's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if OfferStation is acquired by or merged with another company 
  * OfferStation displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. 
  * Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women aged 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
  * OfferStation does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Membership Information and Preferences**  

You can edit your OfferStation membership profile at any time.   
New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.   
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the OfferStation service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the OfferStation Newsletter, that are considered part of your OfferStation account.   
Changes to this Privacy Policy

OfferStation reserves the right to modify, update, and change this policy at our discretion at any time.   

[

## GrabCar 100% Ride Guarantee Promotion

](http://www.offerstation.com/offers-promotions/180655/grabcar-100-percent-ride-guarantee-promotion.htm)

[

## Bosch Year End Bargain

](http://www.offerstation.com/warehouse-sales/180171/bosch-year-end-bargain.htm)

[

## New Naughty Nuri's Warung at Atria Shopping Gallery

](http://www.offerstation.com/dining-food-offers/178505/new-naughty-nuris-warung-at-atria-shopping-gallery.htm)

[

## Uncle Tetsu Cheesecake Festive Promotion

](http://www.offerstation.com/dining-food-offers/180523/uncle-tetsu-cheesecake-festive-promotion.htm)

[

## Perfect Lifestyle '16 Home & Living Exhibition

](http://www.offerstation.com/happenings-events/180787/perfect-lifestyle-16-home-and-living-exhibition.htm)

[

## Olive Garden Lobster Fettuccine Promotion

](http://www.offerstation.com/dining-food-offers/180849/olive-garden-lobster-fettuccine-promotion.htm)

[

## New Hokkaido Baked Cheese Tart Outlet at Mahkota Parade

](http://www.offerstation.com/dining-food-offers/178748/new-hokkaido-baked-cheese-tart-outlet-at-mahkota-parade.htm)

[

## Philips Warehouse Clearance

](http://www.offerstation.com/warehouse-sales/180878/philips-warehouse-clearance.htm)
